Samo Davis

DIGITAL MARKETER PROJECT MANAGER

Content manager with track record of successfully managing multiple projects in a fast-paced environment. Strong team player with excellent analytical and relationship management skills who translates business needs and requirements into a great customer experience.

Employment

The Durst Organization, NY, NY

Manager of Digital Content - May 2016 to February 2018

- Create and manage social media team and presence through content creation, strategy, SEO/ SEM, and digital advertising
- Consistency of brand content across web portfolio through web design, development coordination and analytical reporting
- Audio visual vendor coordination and installation management of marketing stops

Digital Content Administrator - July 2013 to May 2016

- Developed and managed content through coordination with marketing team, web team and consultants for commercial portfolio with a main project focus of One World Trade Center
- Audio visual and presentation management for content consistency

Project Coordinator - January 2011 to July 2013

- Collaborated with marketing team to manage New York Water Taxi's social media and web
- Managed team and document compilation for adAPT Micro housing RFP
- Coordinated with Chief Marketing Officer to improve the structural design of shared information environments and branding within the existing property portfolio
- Managed the Carvel Property Development Project work orders, invoice processing, budgeting and workflow
- Assisted with AutoCad tenant fit out drawings for portfolio properties

Special Projects Administrator - July 2009 to January 2011

- Managed meeting planning and logistics for company events
- Assisted with projects, presentations, meeting scheduling, analysis, data-capture, and file organization
- · Created budget and workflow spreadsheets for projects
- Assisted with creation of company intranet, company filing protocols, and hot files

Stephen Burrows, NY, NY

Consultant - Fall 2008 to July 2009; Intern Summer 2008

- Coordinated with vendors in preparation for annual fashion show
- Edited web content for accuracy, onsistency of content, and design basic web design HTML

Education

New York Code and Design Academy, New York, New York

Certificate, User Interface & User Experience Design 101 - May 2018

General Assembly, New York, New York

Certificate, Front End Web Development - April 2018

Parsons The New School for Design, New York, New York

Associate in Applied Science, Fashion - May 2009

Sarah Lawrence College

Bachelor of Arts, Creative Writing, Japanese, & Sculpture - May 2007

21 West 120th Street, Apt 2 New York, New York 10027

(203) 722-4049 samomillerdavis@gmail.com

Skills

General:

74 WPM

Project Management

File Management

Design Production

Copy Creation / Editing

Content / Campaign Strategy

Design/ Office Software:

Adobe Creative Suite

AutoCad (basic)

Microsoft Creative Suite

Google Suite

Web:

Sketch

SEO / SEM

HTML / CSS

UX / UI

Google Analytics / Google Adwords Google Data Studio

Elevator/Signage programing:

S2 / Elite PI Designer/transfer /

Total Channel

Project Management:

Pivotal Tracker / Basecamp / Asana / Function Fox

Chat:

Hip Chat / Slack

Social Media:

Hootsuite / Meltwater / Talkwalker Instagram / LinkedIn / Facebook Facebook Business / Twitter

Email Marketing:

Mailchimp / Act-on / Constant Contact **UTM** coding

File management:

Google Drive / Sharefile / Drop Box / Open Asset

3D Scans

Matterport Scans / VR